{
    "id": "2ddc9f37e6a54bc182d62b4bd403c9f6",
    "title": "Irregular Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is ................................. on mischief.",
            "description": "The past participle of bend is bent.",
            "answers": [
                "bend",
                "bended",
                "bent"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ..................................... them for a long time.",
            "description": "We use the past participle form of the verb after has, have or had.",
            "answers": [
                "knowed",
                "knew",
                "known"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Political conflict has ........................................ the nation.",
            "description": "The past participle of tear is torn.",
            "answers": [
                "tore",
                "torn",
                "teared"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The kitten .................................... a hole in the curtain.",
            "description": "The past simple form of tear is tore.",
            "answers": [
                "teared",
                "tore",
                "torn"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The man was ............................................. by a speeding vehicle.",
            "description": "The past participle of hit is hit.",
            "answers": [
                "hit",
                "hitted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The house was .............................................. among the trees.",
            "description": "The past participle of hide is hidden.",
            "answers": [
                "hided",
                "hidden",
                "hid"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The farmer was .......................................... by the dog.",
            "description": "The past participle of bite is bitten.",
            "answers": [
                "bite",
                "byte",
                "bitten"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Last winter the water pipes ....................................... in the cold weather.",
            "description": "Burst has only one form - burst",
            "answers": [
                "burst",
                "bursted",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ my hand yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "burnt",
                "burned",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The hikers ............................................ their way up the hill.",
            "description": "The past of wind is wound.",
            "answers": [
                "winded",
                "wound",
                "wounded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The sweater has ............................................ thin at the elbows.",
            "description": "The past participle of wear is worn.",
            "answers": [
                "wore",
                "worn",
                "worned"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Much water has ....................................................... under the bridge.",
            "description": "Flown is the past participle of flow.",
            "answers": [
                "flowed",
                "flew",
                "flown"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}